

Gautham Chandra

About

I am a college student at the University of Oklahoma majoring in Aeronautical/Aerospace engineering. Some of my strengths include creativity, time management, and organization.

Contact

(209)637-0490

chandra.gautham@gmail.com

https://gauthamc.me/

Norman, Oklahoma

Expertise

Time Management $\bigstar \bigstar \bigstar \bigstar$ Communication $\bigstar \bigstar \bigstar \bigstar$ Problem Solving $\bigstar \bigstar \bigstar \bigstar$ Creativity

Leadership ★★★

Communication ★★★↑

Work Experience



Youth Tribune 2018 - 2022

Vice-President

Youth Tribune is a non-profit organization that strives to help foster children excel. As the vice president of the organization, I:

- Helped organize and set up events and fundraisers
- Coordinated with the board to plan future programs



Vector Marketing

2022 - Present

Sales associate

I am working as a sales associate for Vector Marketing and as a sales associate, I have:

- Communicated with team members and managers about product details
- Sold products to customers
- Kept a organized schedule to manage my time between work and home

Education



Mountain House High School 2018 - 2022 High School Diploma



University of Oklahoma 2022 - Present BA Aerospace Engineering